const triviaQuestions = [
  {
    questionId: 1,
    category: "TV Sitcoms",
    question: "What was Kramer's first name on the TV show Seinfeld?",
    answer1: "Newman",
    answer2: "Kevin",
    answer3: "Roswell",
    answer4: "Cosmo",
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
  {
    questionId: 2,
    category: "TV Sitcoms",
    question:
      "On the TV show Friends, what is the name of the song that Phoebe often sang at the Coffee House?",
    answer1: "Alley Cat",
    answer2: "Silly Cat",
    answer3: "Smelly Cat",
    answer4: "Jelly Cat",
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },

  {
    questionId: 3,
    category: "Literature",
    question:
      "In a famous 19th century novel, who or what did the captain and crew of the ship Pequod hunt for?",
    answer1: "Frankenstein",
    answer2: "The white whale, Moby Dick",
    answer3: "A Great White shark",
    answer4: "Captain Nemo",
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    questionId: 4,
    category: "literature",
    question: "Who was the group of people who followed Robin Hood?",
    answer1: "The Mighty Men",
    answer2: "The Happy Hooligans",
    answer3: "The Goofy Guys",
    answer4: "The Merry Men",
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
  {
    questionId: 5,
    category: "Astronomy",
    question: "What is the average distance between the Earth and Sun?",
    answer1: "93 million miles",
    answer2: "238,000 miles",
    answer3: "241 million miles",
    answer4: "1 light year",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 6,
    category: "Astronomy",
    question:
      "In the northern hemisphere, the best known constellation in the sky is probably Ursa Major. By what name do we commonly call this constellation?",
    answer1: "The Big Dipper",
    answer2: "The Northern Lights",
    answer3: "The Milky Way",
    answer4: "Andromeda",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 7,
    category: "Sports",
    question:
      "What baseball player still holds the record for most at bats, most hits and most games played in a career?",
    answer1: "Lou Gehrig",
    answer2: "Cal Ripken Jr.",
    answer3: "Pete Rose",
    answer4: "Steve Garvey",
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    questionId: 8,
    category: "Basic Civics",
    question:
      "Article 1 of the US Constitution defines the powers of what branch of the US government?",
    answer1: "The Legislative branch",
    answer2: "The Executive branch",
    answer3: "The Militiary branch",
    answer4: "The Judicial branch",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 9,
    category: "Movies",
    question:
      "Name the movie with this famous quote: 'Open the pod bay doors, HAL'.",
    answer1: "Titanic",
    answer2: "Star Wars",
    answer3: "2001: A Space Odyssey",
    answer4: "Gone With The Wind",
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    questionId: 10,
    category: "Science",
    question:
      "Geological Eras are measured in millions of years. In what geological era did the dinosaurs live?",
    answer1: "Paleozoic Era",
    answer2: "Mesozoic Era",
    answer3: "Cenozoic Era",
    answer4: "Precambrian Era",
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    questionId: 11,
    category: "Geography",
    question:
      "Ten of the 12 countries in South America border an ocean. Which of these countries is completely landlocked?",
    answer1: "Ecuador",
    answer2: "Columbia",
    answer3: "Guyana",
    answer4: "Bolivia",
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
  {
    questionId: 12,
    category: "Music",
    question:
      "In 1956, Elvis Presley said he found a new place to dwell. What was its name?",
    answer1: "Heartbreak Hotel",
    answer2: "Blueberry Hill",
    answer3: "Viva Las Vegas",
    answer4: "Jailhouse Rock",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 13,
    category: "Astronomy",
    question: "What planet has 2 moons named Phobos and Deimos?",
    answer1: "Jupiter",
    answer2: "Mars",
    answer3: "Pluto",
    answer4: "Venus",
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    questionId: 14,
    category: "Astronomy",
    question: "What is the Large Magellanic Cloud?",
    answer1: "A nebula made of of gas and debris",
    answer2: "An asteroid belt in our Solar System",
    answer3: "A small galaxy near the Milky Way",
    answer4: "A cluster of galaxies in the constellation Virgo",
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    questionId: 15,
    category: "Sports",
    question: "Who was the last baseball player to bat over .400 for a season?",
    answer1: "Ty Cobb",
    answer2: "Joe DiMaggio",
    answer3: "Shoeless Joe Jackson",
    answer4: "Ted Williams",
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
  {
    questionId: 16,
    category: "History",
    question:
      "How many US Presidents have been removed from office through the impeachemt process?",
    answer1: "Zero",
    answer2: "1",
    answer3: "2",
    answer4: "3",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 17,
    category: "Canadian Trivia",
    question:
      "If a Canadian gives you a Loonie, what would you likely do with it?",
    answer1: "Catch a fish with it",
    answer2: "Spend it",
    answer3: "Eat it",
    answer4: "Drink it",
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    questionId: 18,
    category: "Science",
    question: "In what field of science would you use a sling psychrometer?",
    answer1: "Meteorology",
    answer2: "Geology",
    answer3: "Particle physics",
    answer4: "Astronomy",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 19,
    category: "Movies",
    question:
      "What movie has this quote: 'You keep saying that word. I do not think it means what you think it means.'?",
    answer1: "Raiders of the Lost Ark",
    answer2: "Back to the Future",
    answer3: "The Princess Bride",
    answer4: "Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid",
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    questionId: 20,
    category: "History",
    question:
      "In what year did the first commercial television station broadcast?",
    answer1: "1918",
    answer2: "1928",
    answer3: "1938",
    answer4: "1948",
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    questionId: 21,
    category: "Vocabulary",
    question: "What is the literal translaton of the French term cul-de-sac?",
    answer1: "Dead end",
    answer2: "Circle",
    answer3: "Turn around",
    answer4: "Bottom of the bag",
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
  {
    questionId: 22,
    category: "History",
    question: "Who was the first US president to die while in office?",
    answer1: "William Henry Harrison",
    answer2: "Abraham Lincoln",
    answer3: "James Garfield",
    answer4: "Zachary Taylor",
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];
let triviaArray = [
  0,
  1,
  2,
  3,
  4,
  5,
  6,
  7,
  8,
  9,
  10,
  11,
  12,
  13,
  14,
  15,
  16,
  17,
  18,
  19,
  20,
  21,
];
